[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":122492,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":373784,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure t hat when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":7039,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":380830,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":9969,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":390801,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1451,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":392255,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3374,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":395631,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1167,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":396800,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your  result. )","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["6","0"],"rt":5878,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":402679,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1352,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":404033,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3254,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":407289,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub>  1 = 2 be cause 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1022,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":408312,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2294,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":410607,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":973,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":411584,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with  the firs t number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2258,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":413845,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":867,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":414714,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2516,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":417232,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":901,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":418135,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2440,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":420577,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1844,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":422422,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2638,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":425061,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":980,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":426043,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, yo u subtra ct 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":2415,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":428459,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":2122,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":430585,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":13121,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":443709,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":55567,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":499280,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":11581,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":510864,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1642,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":512509,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3614,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":516124,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":926,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":517052,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"Wha t is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2784,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":519838,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":914,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":520754,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2296,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":523051,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":745,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":523797,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2808,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":526606,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":3604,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":530211,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":71776,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":601989,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub >6</sub> . <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":55629,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":657627,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":11884,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":669520,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":9334,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":678857,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":5983,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":684843,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":31629,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":716474,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a g enerator  under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":5242,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":721718,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1402,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":723122,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":3846,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":726970,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1454,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":728426,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the  remaini ng questions as accurately as possible.","rt":39227,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":767656,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4072,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":771736,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1121,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":772859,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3409,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":776270,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2175,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":778446,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2943,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":781391,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2261,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":783653,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2321,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":785975,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5. 4+1 is under 9 so that is the answer","response_history":["5. I added","5. I adde","5. I add","5. I ad","5. I a","5. I ","5. I","5. 4+1 is under 9 so that is the answer"],"rt":25426,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":811402,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"4    8+4=13 which is greater than 9 so you do 14-9 to get 4","response_history":["4    8+4 is","4    8+4 i","4    8+4 ","4    8+4=13 which is greater than 9 so you do 14-9 to get 4"],"rt":26720,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":838124,"internal_chunk_id":" 0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"This One I am unsure about.  I thought I understood it but then got a few wrong in the examples and was still confused","response_history":["Thius ","Thius","Thiu","This One I am unsure about.  I was trying to figure it out from the examples but am still confused","This One I am unsure about.  I thought I understood it but then got a feew","This One I am unsure about.  I thought I understood it but then got a fee","This One I am unsure about.  I thought I understood it but then got a few wrong in the examples and could","This One I am unsure about.  I thought I understood it but then got a few wrong in the examples and coul","This One I am unsure about.  I thought I understood it but then got a few wrong in the examples and cou","This One I am unsure about.  I thought I understood i t but th en got a few wrong in the examples and co","This One I am unsure about.  I thought I understood it but then got a few wrong in the examples and c","This One I am unsure about.  I thought I understood it but then got a few wrong in the examples and was still confused"],"rt":175329,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1013456,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":9583,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1023054,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":3627,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1026685,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12 -0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","response_history":["9"],"rt":8991,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1035677,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6.  You take 3+x=9 where x is the inverse.  and 3+6=9","response_history":["6.","6  The inverse is what number","6 ","6.  T","6.  You take 3+x=9 to get the","6.  You take 3+x=9 to get th","6.  You take 3+x=9 to get t","6.  You take 3+x=9 to get ","6.  You take 3+x=9 to get","6.  You take 3+x=9 to ge","6.  You take 3+x=9 to g","6.  You take 3+x=9 to ","6.  You take 3+x=9 to","6.  You take 3+x=9 t","6.  You take 3+x=9 where x is the inverse.  and 3+6=9"],"rt":69615,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1105293,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"This one I am also unsure about and got it confused with the identity ","response_history":["I can not rem","No bevause ","No bevause","No bevaus","No bevau","No beva","No bev","No becuase i","This oe ","This oe","This one I am also us","This one I am also unsure about and got in","This one I am also unsure about and got it confused with the identity "],"rt":64621,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1169923,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Same response as the last one I am confused by the generator part of  it","response_history":["Same response as the last one I am cons","Same response as the last one I am confused by the generator part of it"],"rt":19824,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1189753,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Same as the last I am confused by this generator concept ","response_history":["Sam as","Sam a","Sam ","Same as the last I am s","Same as the last I am confused by this generator concept "],"rt":14480,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1204235,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Same as last I am confused by this generator c oncept","response_history":["Sae","Same as last I am confused by this generator concept"],"rt":10398,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1214634,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":11679,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1226314,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1+(+n-x)","response_history":["1++n","1+)+n","1++n","1+)+n","1++n","1+(+n-x)"],"rt":91098,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1317415,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"I have no idea...this question is too hard for me.","response_history":["inverse of x is ","I have no idea...this question is too hard for me."],"rt":434115,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1751543,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I have no idea.  I was trying to find one but could not","response_history":["I have no idea.  I was trying to find one but could not"],"rt":17217,"trial_type":"questio n","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1768768,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":8178,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1776949,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":3981,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1780933,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi ","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":6061,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1786995,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"I am sorry I have no idea and any answer I would give would be a guess","response_history":["I am sorry I have no idea and any answer I would give owuld be a guess","I am sorry I have no idea and any answer I would give would be a guess"],"rt":61009,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1848006,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or nev er?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":9752,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1857763,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"I have no clue anything I write is just a guess I do not even know where to start","response_history":["I have no clue.","I have no cluem","I have no clue, andy","I have no clue, and","I have no clue, any","I have no clue, an","I have no clue, a","I have no clue, ","I have no clue,","I have no clue any gues","I have no clue any gue","I have no clue any gu","I have no clue any g","I have no clue any ","I have no cl ue anyth ing I write is just a guess I do not even know where to start"],"rt":31204,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1888970,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":14501,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1903472,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1998,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1905474,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":" 25","response_history":["25"],"rt":2065,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1907540,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":3127,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1910668,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I took a low level calculus class in college.  It may have been pre-Calculus  but I am  not sure","response_history":["College level Calculus, man","College level Calculus, ma","College level Calculus, m","College level Calculus, ","College level Calculus,","College level Calculus","College level Calculu","I took Ca","I took C","I took a low level calculus cas in college.","I took a low level calculus clas in college.","I took a low level calculus claas in college.","I took a low level calculus clas in college.","I took a low level calculus class in college.  It may have been pre-Calculus but I am not sure"],"rt":54824,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1965493,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":19134,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1984629,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":3921,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1988554,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat ","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3969,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1992525,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3093,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1995619,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2213,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1997833,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":1907,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1999742,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":3753,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2003497,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":3372,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":2006870,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I felt  really c onfused near the last section of the hit when it got into the generators.  If the lessons and examples were on the page as we were given the problem it would be a lot easier to figure out.  Maybe not having the examples on the page was the point though?  I am sorry I was not able to show my work for the last several questions but I did not even know where to start","response_history":["I felt really confused near the last 75% of the hit","I felt really confused near the last section of the hit when it got into the generators.  I feel if","I felt really confused near the last section of the hit when it got into the generators.  I feel if","I felt really confused near the last section of the hit when it got into the generators.  If the lesson ","I felt really confused near the last section of the hit when it got into the generators.  If the lessons and examples were on the page as we were given the problem it would be a lot easier to figure out.  Maybe not having lesso","I fel t really  confused near the last section of the hit when it got into the generators.  If the lessons and examples were on the page as we were given the problem it would be a lot easier to figure out.  Maybe not having less","I felt really confused near the last section of the hit when it got into the generators.  If the lessons and examples were on the page as we were given the problem it would be a lot easier to figure out.  Maybe not having les","I felt really confused near the last section of the hit when it got into the generators.  If the lessons and examples were on the page as we were given the problem it would be a lot easier to figure out.  Maybe not having le","I felt really confused near the last section of the hit when it got into the generators.  If the lessons and examples were on the page as we were given the problem it would be a lot easier to figure out.  Maybe not having l","I felt really confused near the last section of the hit when it got into the generators.  If  the les sons and examples were on the page as we were given the problem it would be a lot easier to figure out.  Maybe not having the examples on the page wer","I felt really confused near the last section of the hit when it got into the generators.  If the lessons and examples were on the page as we were given the problem it would be a lot easier to figure out.  Maybe not having the examples on the page we","I felt really confused near the last section of the hit when it got into the generators.  If the lessons and examples were on the page as we were given the problem it would be a lot easier to figure out.  Maybe not having the examples on the page was the point though?  I am sorry I was not able to show my work for the last few","I felt really confused near the last section of the hit when it got into the generators.  If the lessons and examples were on the page as we were given the problem it would be a lot easier to figure out.  Maybe not having the examples on the page was th e point  though?  I am sorry I was not able to show my work for the last fe","I felt really confused near the last section of the hit when it got into the generators.  If the lessons and examples were on the page as we were given the problem it would be a lot easier to figure out.  Maybe not having the examples on the page was the point though?  I am sorry I was not able to show my work for the last f","I felt really confused near the last section of the hit when it got into the generators.  If the lessons and examples were on the page as we were given the problem it would be a lot easier to figure out.  Maybe not having the examples on the page was the point though?  I am sorry I was not able to show my work for the last several questions but I did not even kn","I felt really confused near the last section of the hit when it got into the generators.  If the lessons and examples were on the page as we were given the problem it would be a lot easier to figure out.  Maybe not having th e exampl es on the page was the point though?  I am sorry I was not able to show my work for the last several questions but I did not even know where to start"],"rt":84776,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":2091648,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]